(Sheldon:)somewhere
beyond our solar system,
(Raj:)going further than anyone
ever thought it could.
Don't leave!
You can do this!
(Bernadette:)Sheldon,
is everything okay?
(Sheldon:)It's too late for Koothrappali.
Let's go!
(Amy:)11 minutes.
That's longer than I thought.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
They're in my shirt!
(Penny:)Okay, this is definitely
the most fun thing we can do
(Penny:)with the money.
(Leonard:)I've never done it on
a big old pile of cash before.
(high-pitched):
"Me neither, Leonard.
It's my first time, too."
(Bernadette:)I'm so sorry I made you feel bad
about the money stuff.
(Howard:)It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
(Bernadette:)I want us to be
partners, equals.
(Bernadette:)Adults in a mature
relationship.
(Howard:)I want that, too.
(Bernadette:)Now, let's talk about
your birthday party.
(Howard:)Ooh, laser tag,
laser tag.
Oh!
(Amy:)Do you really need me
to transcribe this?
(Sheldon:)You're not doing it for me.
(Sheldon:)You're doing it
for future generations
(Sheldon:)who will benefit
from my struggle.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon's Mine Simulation Log,
entry four:
(Sheldon:)my Kit Kat has melted.
(Sheldon:)All is lost.
(Raj:)You call yourself
a friend?!
(Raj:)I was trying
to help you!
And at the first sign of trouble
(Raj:)you ran away, leaving me
to fend off a family of rats!
(Raj:)You're a completely selfish
human being
(Raj:)and a... and a physical
and a moral coward!
(Sheldon:)His statements of the obvious
continue to annoy.